wpdeveloper.net 2013-06-05

# WPDeveloper.net » Privacy Policy

##    [Privacy Policy](http://wpdeveloper.net/privacy-policy/ "Permanent Link to Privacy Policy")  

The privacy of **WPDeveloper.net** users is important to us.  
As a WordPress marketplace, WPDeveloper.net is committed to the security of your information and pledges to follow the terms set out in this **privacy policy** (“Privacy Policy”).

**Public Information**  
Our Website enables you to post information to be accessed by others through our comments. When you do so, other visitors may collect your data and attempt to contact you off the site. WPDeveloper.net cannot be held liable for any offsite communications that result from your posting of personal information on our site. If you do not wish to be contacted offsite by other WPDeveloper.net visitors, do not share your personal information in the content when leaving a comment. Please note: Although you are required to provide your e-mail address in the specified field when entering a comment, your e-mail address will only be available to the WPDeveloper.net website administrators and will not be publicly visible. 

**Advertisers**  
Third-party advertisers featured on WPDeveloper.net may collect tracking information in a different manner than is set out in this Privacy Policy. The only information that they will be able to track is basic Website usage information; e-mail addresses are not passed on to advertisers for any reason even if they are provided to WPDeveloper.net voluntarily.

**Cookies**  
We use cookies to store visitor preferences, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, customize content based on visitor browser type or other information that the visitor sends. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site. Google, through their Adsense Program, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to RedmonePie.com users based on their visit to this and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**Information Ownership**  
All e-mails, comments or other forms of communication received by WPDeveloper.net are the property of WPDeveloper.net and may be used for editorial or technical improvements to the Website at our discretion without any form of compensation being owed to the sender of said communications.

**Information Security**  
We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities and the facilities of our service providers to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our Website.  
Information provided by Website visitors is held in confidence and used for editorial and technical improvements to the Website.

**Joining the site and downloading plugins**  
If you register to join the site in order to upload or download a plugin or a theme or any other product or services we will securely store any details that you provide us with in our databases. We will not share this information with any third party. We may from time to time contact you regarding new products and/or policy changes at WPDeveloper.net, this will be done via email and unsubscription information will be provided with each email.

**Privacy Contact**  
If you feel that this Website is not following this Privacy Policy, you may contact us at with your concerns.
